YURI GALASEVICH

FULL-STACK AND WEBGL DEVELOPER

CONTACT

galasevic.jurij@gmail.com

Vilnius, Lithuania

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jurijgalasevic-mdc

SKILLS

React / React Native / Next

Node / Nest

Vue.js / Nuxt

Unity 2D / 3D

PHP / Laravel

MySQL / PostgreSQL

MongoDB / DynamoDB

Solidity / Web3

Three.js / WebGL

Phaser / Pixi / Cocos2D

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology and Systems

Kyoto University

Sep 2015 - Mar 2019

LANGUAGES

English: Professional

Japanese: Native

Lithuanian: Intermediate

PROFILE

This is Full-Stack & WebGL Developer with over 5 years of experience in developing web, mobile applications and web3 solutions. Proficient in using various front-end and back-end technologies, including Node.js, React.js, Vue.js, Laravel, Three.js, Unity, and Web3.

WORK EXPERIENCE

❖ Full-Stack & WebGL Developer

NovaConcepts - US, Remote

Aug 2023 - Present

- Completely created a website for Sculptures and Photos from A to Z.
- Developed 3D Virtual Store with React.js, Three.js for a new feature.
- Developed Casino Game Platform using React.js, Pixi, Node.js,
 MongoDB and WebSocket (PlayZelo).
- Integrated crypto payment gateway for player financial management using Tatum.io and Binance API.
- Implemented app integration with RESTful APIs for Google Maps, social media logins, several payment processors and other 3rd party services using Laravel, and Node.js.

Full-Stack Developer

Motley Agency – Helsinki, Finland, Remote Oct 2020 – Jun 2023

- Developed interactive 3D web applications, 3D Visualization, 3D Web Games using React.js, Vue.js, Three.js, Unity3D framework.
- Implemented complex 3D animations and visual effects using shaders and WebGL.
- Optimized performance by utilizing efficient rendering techniques and minimizing resource usage.
- Built a dynamic web application using Node.js, Laravel, and React.js frameworks.
- Developed 2D web games using HTML5 game engines like Phaser, Pixi and Cocos2D.